─────────────────
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is seriously too good to be true.
Good evening, everyone.
I'm Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love.
I'm Shoko Takioki.
Yes, this is Hitomi Takamatsu from Equal Love and Shoko Takioki from
Boat Race
We're here at Toda-san!
Last time, we had the first part.
I had a good meal at the race
And we rode a boat.
That's right.
This time, for the second part.
I'm going to win.
I got it last time.
Shoko, a high school student...
And me, the director.
I'm wearing it.
Like this.
I'd like to do it like this.
Today, we'll be looking at races 10 through 12.
Race 12.
We're going to take a look at three races today.
Let's take a look.
And guess what?
Race 10.10 Races
Our first race of the day
What a surprise!
We are going to watch from outside!
Yay!
That's great!
I'm so happy!
I think I'm okay now. Oh, my gosh!
Your voice is a little...
Yes, you do.
I'm worried about you.
I'm sure that if you go out for more than a minute...
I'm sure you'll be able to hear your friends.
I'm sure they're all very vocal.
And today's rules.
Each member will receive 10,000 yen.
For the three races.
10,000 yen. Use it all up.
Yes, we'll use it up.
Yes, sir.
At the end of the races
If there is any money left over
I have not had any yet
If there is
As parts of the Bird Racing Department
I will save it.
Let's keep up the good work.
Wow, that was amazing. That was amazing. Absolutely.
We're gonna win.
We'll win.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.Ha-ha-ha!
Yes, I'll make a quick prediction then.
Let's go for it!
I'm going to win.
I'll take first place in race 10.
I'll take first place...
Oh, wait a minute, first place is not good!
Oh, but 14.5.
14.5?
I don't know.
I learned from the boat racing club.
I learned in boat racing.
I learned that if you don't narrow it down.
I learned that if you don't narrow it down, the birds will see it.
I'm going to box this time.
I talked to the staff.
Box?
I'll do a box.
I'm going to make a box.
Gentlemen of the box.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
Yes, I'll squeeze it! I'm serious.
It's all about the squeeze!
Let's do it!
Okay, I'll do the introduction.
Okay, just write it down.
Okay.
First of all, since it's Hitomi...
I'll give you 300 yen for 13 double tickets.
In the form of a transparency, nyu-tsu.
Ichigo, Zen, in eight ways.Strawberry, Zen, in 8 ways.
It was 2,700 yen.
That means it is acceptable.
Not too much.
Well, I wonder which one will come.
I'll choose the one I like first once.
5x5x5.
It's yellow.
Yes, I'll go with 3,100 yen.
And, for 2,700 yen.
Let's go.
I'm going for the first time.
Oh no.
I'm going to Ramdad for the first time.
Can we put it all together? Yeah, I'm fine.
Go ahead, go ahead.
Yay!
That's great. My first time.
Nice to meet you.
I'm looking forward to meeting you.
Yes, so I've met you, too.
We met.
Yay!
I'm so happy.
I'll see you outside.
Yay!
It's the first time I've seen you outside, too.
I'm so happy.
Let's go home as soon as possible.
Okay, the race is about to start.Then the race will start.
It's really right in front of you.
On the carpet.
De-de-de-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee.
De-de-de-de-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee
Jade-de-de-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee-dee
Ta-da-da-da-da-da!
The stuffed animal was again in the last video, so please watch about this!
It's hard!
The stuffed animal was on error, so let's get it ready for the top!
Next time going to the next movie
I'm done!
Call the navigator appropriately
Wow!
Ending
I wondered why
First time in my life in one shot
I got hit in the hand.
That's great.
Station 29, 8133.
Two in a row. Eleven in a row.
That was a great angle.
That's amazing.
That's so awesome!
That's great.
I'm so happy.
Wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow, wow.
Eleven consecutive opposing centers.
First one, first hole.
Payout payout
First payback.First time paying back
I'll do my best
Open the voting vessel.
please
(in a loud voice)
Wow!
Wow! You did it! We did it! That's great! I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
I've never been back like this before! Yay! Let's win the next one! Let's go for it!
Okay, so we're back! You're still excited, right? My heart! Oh, no!
Oh, no! My heart is racing around here!
But race 11 is coming up, so I'll get right to it and make my prediction for race 11!
No ordinary boat racecourse will bring you here!
Not even the world's first!
No! No!
Thank you! For me!
I can do it! Because it's already a plus!
Whatever happens today, it's a plus!
Thank you! Shoko!
It's a team competition!
You're a genius!
Even if 13 pays, it's still 3 times the price!
So I'm going to buy it as a formality.
But it's going to come, isn't it?
So can I help you with this?
It's almost like you're in charge.
I'm asking you to leave!
Shoko, my pupils don't seem to be so lucky right now.
So I'm going to push all thirteen in a row.
Can I put it in?
And Shoko will box them.
I'm sure one of them will win.One of you will win.
Group competition?
Thank you! Sir!
Hitomi!
Race 11 will be for the Saitama guy from the No. 2 pavilion.
I'll take the 1, 2, 5 box and the 1, 3, 5 box.
I want you to buy it! He's coming!
I'll bet 500 yen on Hatsuko for the two in a row.
And I'll put 300 yen each on the 1, 2, 5 box and the 1, 3, 5 box.
The 1, 3, 5 box is called ?
Miriya box.
It's coming today, Mirinya's birthday box.
13,400 yen, 3,600 yen!
Thanks to Shoko! I can use it like this!
Let's go buy it! Let's go buy some!
I'm so glad I feel comfortable.
Thanks to Shoko!
One, three, one, three, one, three, one, three, one, three, one, three, one, three, one, three, one, three!
But this is seriously good.
One, two, five?
If you get a 1,2,5 box, you're in for a real treat!
Pushy face! I'm really pushing for it!
Come on! Here we go.
Eleven races.
Oh, no! It's starting!
Race 11, let's go!
Oh!
Oh, my gosh!
Pie, pie, pie, pie.
It's a screen already. I like that one. I like that one.
One, three, that's good!1,3 is good!
Yeah, I'm good.
I'm in! I'm going!
Go for it! You can do it!
Woooo!
Oh, my gosh! Oh, I thought you were coming. Hold on.
One, two, five?
One... four! Four!
Oh, it's coming! Uh, hey, if we don't get a four...
Okay! One, two, five, three, one!
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right!
Not again! I want proof!
Evidence box! I like the evidence box!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
I got it, I got it, I got it! One, two...
Go! Oh!
Ohhh!
Go! Come on! One, two, five!
Go! One, two, five!
Yeah! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on!
Chin.
Aaah! Why? Why? Why?
I don't know yet!
You don't know yet, do you?
It's a little bit... It changes a lot next door.
It changes with every turn.
I can do it. I can do it.
Five!
I don't have any more.
Shoko's one, two, three.Shoko's one, two, three.
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it.
Last last thrust.
My body is bent.
I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go!
I can go, I can go, I can go, I can go
I can do it! I can do it! I can do it!
It was 5, right?
It was one, two, five.
It was 1,2,5 at the end.
5 was before.
kernel
ana
Oh, my God!
That was amazing!
Oh, man! Oh, man!
Oh, man!
Oh, my God, Shoko!
1,580 yen!
You're winning again!
Me?
Well, we just did it as a group.
Thank you.
You're so sweet.
What? A little bit.
Oh, my God.
Your eyes are all dilated.
I've increased them again, Shoko.
All that study was worth it.All that studying was worth it.
No, really!
Now, what is that?
Huh? Huh?
Oh, my gosh! Let's do it this year!
Yay! I'm so happy!
Do you want to put in your marker card or your ballot?
Yes!
There's an extraordinary boy!
I'm so happy!
I'm like, what?
I'm going to support Shoko as much as I can. I'm...
Let's go for it! Let's go for it! I'll cheer Shoko on all the way, today too!
So, now that the 11th race is over, I'd like to make a prediction for the 12th and final race.
As of this moment, Shoko's recovery rate is amazingly high!
Yes! 437%! Yay! That's great!
I have a dream!
No, really, I thought. I thought, "I'm doing it. I have a dream. I have a dream!
I have zero!
I'm losing all my games behind Shoko's back. I hope she wins till the end. I hope she wins next time. I hope she wins!
Then, let's predict! Yes! Yes, sir!
What happened to the 4th boat? Does Mr. Ishibashi like the sixth boat?
What's the situation? The 4 starts on the 6? Yes, he did.
4 is very unmotivated. He's very motivated. Because why did 4 go this way?
What's going on? Maybe Shoko's hot. If 4 is motivated.
Sure.
I can feel it. I feel like 4 is going to make him crazy.
Shoko. I'll totally give it to you. Shoko.
10,000 at the end. I want to win.
That's right.Yes, that's right.
Let's put it on something weird.
So let's buy a weird one.
Sashiara-san! Sashiara-san's!
I've come this far, I've almost given up. I'm sure Shouko will guess it for me.
Guess?
But my dad just arrived.
I'm sure one will come.
I knew he would come.
And he's from Saitama branch.
We're running out of time. Four minutes.
I think I'll go for 1, 2, all.
Race 12.
I've got Shoko for 200 yen on the 2-horse.
And in the box.
1,2,5 and 1,5,6.
I'm off.
Last race.
It's the last.
Give me strength now.
Okay, let's do it this way.
But, Shoco, you're looking good this time.
Two, two, all in five.
We'll hit it together.
And one, five, six.
We can do it.
We can do it again.
I'm getting power.
I've changed.
It's true.
I'm going to course six in four.I knew 4 want to go to course 6.
Shoko might be hot too.
Wait a minute.
I knew it!
I want to go to course six.
Oh, my God, they're going in.
They're going in. They're going in. They're going in.
Four!
Five!
Five? - Yeah!
I'm just saying I want a four!
We're at 4, 5!
I can do it, I can do it, I can do it!
We're at 4 and 5!
Come on!
I'm at four or five!
I can do it! Come on!
I got it!
What, two hits?
Two hits!
I knew it from the start page.
The 4 that was in the rod course
It's now a one!
So you're saying I should've won
I should have won the four?
I'm screwed.
I don't know about that.
Four-five.
4-5, evidence.
Maybe I'll just call it evidence.Might as well be evidence.
Wow, but it's 4-5.
You got it all right.
I put evidence on all of them.
I got it.
That's great. That's great.
Four-five-one-five.
And he only made it to 200 at the end.
You have and you don't have today.
I'm having it and I'm not having it today.
Oh, wait, I'm so lucky.
I'm so lucky.
Wait.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's not paper at all.
Two hundred yen.
It's very, very strong!
Eighty-six hundred yen.
Yay!
I'm so happy!
We won the whole thing!
200!
That's really bad!
That's too much!
What? That's so bad!
My day!
What? Oh, my God!
I'm so glad I made it 200 yen.
Oh, thank God! I just happened to have some left over.Thank goodness!!! I just happened to have some left over.
Gorgeous!
Two hits in a row brings 8,000!
Yay!
I won it all!
Nobody wins everything.
Not even boat racers.
Winning all 10, 11, 12.
Wow.
I'm so happy!
Okay, here we go for race 12.
Please insert your ballot or
Press the payment sensor button.
YEAH!
Ha!
Thank you very much.
I'm back.
That's great!
That's great.
Thank you so much.
I can't.
Yes, sir.
We're down to 12 races.
Finished.
This time, the evidence is in.
Total
28270 yen
GACHI
Yay!Yay!
And I'm minus 10,000 yen.
Yay!
Even if we still have to borrow together.
18,270 yen.
another look
Well then, today was really the first time I ended up with such a positive balance!
Yay, I'm so happy!
This, 28,270 yen
As parts of the boat racing club
As a part of the boat racing club
I'll leave it with the staff.
We'll ask them to increase it again.
Someone else will make it more.
I'm sure I'll melt it down again.
It was great, thank you, Shuka!
I enjoyed both the first part and the second part
I have a dry throat
Both the first part and the second part are dying in my throat
Maybe some of you haven't seen the first part.
I hope you will see both!
So, that's all.
The best!
It was the 4th edition of Equal Love Boat Racing Club!
Thank you, Shuka!
Thank you very much.
Please come back and watch again!
Bye bye!